ztod.com 2018-11-18

# Privacy Info

#### Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the following websites: (1) www.ztod.com (collectively, the "Sites", or individually, a "Site").

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Sites. By accessing and using our Sites, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Sites. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

### About The Information We Collect

We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Sites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points throughout our Sites.

### What Data We Collect and Why

When you use our service we collect the following data from you:

  * Your **viewing history** , **page views** , **search queries** so that we can tailor content discovery better for you. 
  * Your **IP Address** to tailor content based on a general location. 
  * We collect **device information** (computers, mobile phones, tablets, etc.). This information includes device specific identifiers and information such as IP address, cookie information, mobile device and advertising identifiers, browser version, operating system type and version, mobile network information, device settings, and software data. So that we can recognize your devices to provide you with personalized experiences. 

When you subscribe to our website we collect the following data from you:

  * Your **email** , **username** and **password** so that you can login to our website. 
  * Your **IP address** so we can determine your general location and keep your account safe and secure. 
  * Your **name** , **country** , **zip** or **postal code** , and **billing information** so that we can charge you for any services on our website. 

### Keeping Your Data Secure

All of your data is stored securely on our servers located in the USA. We implement industry standard technology for maintaining the security of all personal information collected by our website.

While we use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to secure your personal information, the transmission of information via the Internet can never be one hundred percent secure. As a result, we can assume no liability if information relating to any subscriber is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient.

**How Long We Store Your Data**

Unless you ask us to delete your data, we will store this information indefinitely to give you continued access to our services.

### Who We Share Your Data With

We only share your data when required for operation of our website and these companies all follow the same security standards as we do. In the future we may change who we share your data with and we will update this page accordingly.

We share your data with the following companies:

  * **CCBill** , **Epoch** or **Segpay** for billing. When you signup to our website, we may share your billing information with these companies to charge you for our service. You will clearly see on the billing gateway page which company will process your data. 
  * **YNOTmail** for marketing. We use YNOTmail to process our email campaigns and share your email, name, country and IP address with them to send you email that you requested. 

### Registration and Order Forms

In order to gain access to our Site, you may be requested to provide us with your date of birth. In addition, in order to purchase goods and services from our Sites, or to become a member of our Sites, a user must complete the on-line registration/order form. During registration, a user is required to provide us with certain contact information (which may include your name, mailing address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address). If we have trouble processing an order or otherwise need to contact a user, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Sites. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Sites, we are able track IP addresses and browser preferences in order to enhance and personalize your experience at our Sites. We may also use cookies in order to track referral sites in order to properly compensate our affiliates. Please note that some of our business partners may also use cookies on our Sites (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### Profiling

From time to time, we may combine personal information and preferences collected on-line with personal information and preferences collected off-line in order to enhance and personalize our services.

### Sharing

We may share aggregated demographic information with our sponsors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may also use an outside company or companies to process payments or to fulfill orders. From time to time, we may contract with another party to provide certain specific services to our users. If we have collected your personally identifiable information from one Site, that Site may share the information with other Sites within our network in order to provide you with additional goods and services for which we believe you may be interested.

Except as provided above, we do not currently sell or otherwise make available personally identifiable information about our users to third parties. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to make such information available to third parties in the future in order to enhance and personalize our services, or in the case of bankruptcy, sale of an asset, business or division, a merger or acquisition, or similar change of ownership.

### Law Enforcement

We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. We will also notify the appropriate authorities if we suspect that any of our users are engaged in illegal activities, such as obscenity or child pornography.

### Links

The Sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Sites they should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

### Security

We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures.

Third Party Sources of Information

From time to time and in order to enhance our services, we may supplement the information we receive from you with information we obtain from third party sources.

### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as phone number), or if a user no longer desires our service, you may contact us to correct or update this information.

### Choice/Opt-out

From time to time, we may send our users e-mail or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us.

### Notification of Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Sites. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use any of our Sites, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use any of our Sites after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice).

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your password, user name and account number so we can service you quicker. 

For www.ztod.com and its related sites, please [contact us](mailto:support@ztod.com).
